<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rss</string>
    <string name="news">News</string>
    <string name="description">A day after unveiling its Nipashe news dream team, Citizen TV has now revealed it’s marquee line up for its 9PM news.

The new all-star line up sees Jeff Koinange join the Citizen TV news team which has a galaxy of stars that include; Ann Kiguta, Hussein Mohammed, Victoria Rubadiri, Lillian Muli, Yvonne Okwara, Waihiga Mwaura and Jacque Maribe.

The revamped show, which is the undisputed prime-time leader in the country, sees Waihiga Mwaura move from mid-morning to prime time and will be paired with Jacque Maribe.

Jeff Koinange will be bringing you the latest news from across the country together with Victoria Rubadiri.

The company has revamped in an effort to continue setting the standards and completely dominating the Kenyan media landscape.</string>

    <string name="sports">Talks are continuing between Arsenal and Aaron Ramsey over a new contract for the Wales international, Sky Sports News understands.

The midfielder has one year left on his current deal and securing his future is believed to be a big priority for Gunners\' head coach Unai Emery as he continues to shape his squad ahead of his first season in charge.

"I'm very happy with him," Emery said of Ramsey last week. "Every day every training session he is with the ambition I want. He is working with quality. I want to work with him." Asked why Ramsey has yet to sign a new deal, Emery added: "This is one question for the player, the club, but my opinion - I said to them - I think he is one important player for me." Arsenal manager Unai Emery reveals there is only one scenario in which another signing might arrive before the current transfer window ends. </string>

    <string-array name="items">
        <item>News</item>
        <item>Sports</item>
        <item>Business</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>News coming in</item>
        <item>Latest sport news coming from the sports center</item>
        <item>Business news coming in</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
